Right now, you want to ask God for His favour and His mercy.
Whatever we say here, let be said in Heaven,
Whatever we shall do, let it be done in Heaven.
Amen.
Ask for the favour and mercy of God. Prayer!
Mercy and favour.
Open your lips. Whatever unbelief spirit i n your heart,
every doubt in your heart, begin to break the spirit, in Jesus' name!
Unbelief!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ
Amen!
When we enter the Inner Courts, the Holy of holies, I will know.
That is when we can begin to ask.
Then, the table will be set before you.
Right on the table every essential of life
Right now, open your lips now and say, "Here I am, contact me, oh Holy Spirit!
Contact me, connect me, oh Holy Spirit!
Here I am, Connect me, oh Holy Spirit! Prayer!
Deliverance In Jesus' name
Say, Here I am, connect me, oh Holy Spirit
Manifestation Of Evil Spirit
Ask Him to locate you.
Locate me, Lord!
Deliverance In Jesus' name
That spirit of sickness, failure, setback, bareness, limitation, begin to break it!
Break it!
Say, Every spirit of failure, limitation, sickness and disease, begin to break it!
In the name of Jesus! Break it!
Deliverance In Jesus' name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Listen! I command that spirit to get out of you!
I command that spirit, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Say out!
I can't hear you.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Whatever spirit that is not of God, that is tormenting you, say out!
I command the spirit
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Deliverance in Jesus' name
In the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Deliverance in Jesus' name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Whatever you might have eaten through dreams
from the table of the enemy that is causing disease. sickness
marital problem or trouble, in the name of Jesus, be flushed out!
Begin to flush out!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Eternal life
I want to live eternal life
God save my soul
Oh my saviour
If you have not known the Lord, confess along with me,
Lord, Jesus I'm a sinner. Come into my heart.
Wash me with Your precious blood. Save my soul today.
My Saviour, thank you for my salvation
I'm delivered today. Thank you for my deliverance.
I'm saved today. Thank you for my salvation.
I'm blessed today. Thank you for my blessing.
I'm healed today. Thank you for my healing.
Eternal life
I want to live eternal life
God save my soul
Oh my Saviour
When You come to collect Your people
Remember me oh Lord
Amen!
TT Monica Asefa